i need to repeat anything
sorry there was a little bit of a
technical glitch there just waiting to
make sure
everything's okay
as i said uh uh every uh if you're
newcomer you're welcome there's lots of
resources available
for you i would ask you all to help me
uh to reach as many people as possible
so that i can help them
by liking this stream to increase its
visibility in the youtube
algorithm at the end of every session
there
is a q a period please limit the
questions
at that time to anything from the whole
ecology of practices
on monday wednesday and friday we give
priority to questions concerning the
western wisdom tradition
and on tuesdays and thursdays we give
priority
to questions concerning the eastern
wisdom traditions
we generally go a little bit longer on
monday wednesdays and fridays
i think that's everything boy all the
all the announcements are sort of piling
up
now today if you have more general
questions we're going to have
our general q a live streamed at 3 p.m
eastern time
on on on youtube and so i uh
welcome you uh to come bring questions
and the questions there
huge range they can range from the very
practical
to the very philosophical
right so
let's get ourselves into position
let's set our phones on do not disturb
we'll begin with some chanting then
we'll move into a silent set
and then we'll take some q a we'll do a
q a we'll take some questions
we'll all begin together when i say
begin
[Music]
one
on
[Music]
one
um
begin your sound set
you
[Music]
slowly come out of your practice trying
as best you can to integrate what you
cultivated in your practice
with your everyday consciousness
cognition character and communicate
perhaps by reciting the five promises
so a reminder of the the new question
schedules monday
wednesdays and fridays emphasizing
the western traditions found in the
wisdom of hypatia
and tuesday and thursday the eastern
wisdom traditions from
ghana from buddhism and davis also a
reminder if people could please share
observations
edifications as well as questions that
would be very helpful
so it looks like we don't have any
questions for today
so maybe you guys are saving them up for
the
live q a this afternoon at 3.
thank you all for joining amara was not
here today
so jason was running everything so
thanks again to my beloved son
please subscribe to this channel to be
notified of the next video you'll find
links there uh to the lecture series
awakening from the meaning crisis
and to the dialogue series voices with
raviki
please also follow me on twitter for
updates about these streams
and for any uh late uh sort of
late and urgent i mean um recent
urgent trying to get the right adjective
different times of time
tenses temporal tensions tension on here
so
please follow me on twitter so you can
get the the most recent
and perhaps most urgent uh updates of
anything concerning
uh the meetings on the sango or any
talks i'm going to be giving
or any alterations uh to any of the
other
live stream projects or video projects
uh please invite others who might
benefit by sharing this series
um there's a lot still going on
and
the different countries are experiencing
this differently there's significant
differences between canada united states
um but even where it's getting better
in a medical sense i think this second
transition
for those of us who are sort of coming
out of the peak of the pandemic
i think this is going to be challenging
in a way that people don't
readily anticipate and i think a lot of
the pent up
hunger for meaning and for connection
and some of the distortions and mental
health challenges
that accrued during this time are also
going to be expressing themselves
more and more of course they've already
been expressing themselves a lot
but we're going to come more and more to
the fore
so we need to sow the seeds
now as much as possible
and i ask you to help me reach out
to as many people as possible
please join the discord server to chat
with others do a group
lectio which i hear is wonderful
the group movement practices another
second sitting
a meditation contemplation sitting
there's also discussion groups
i'm there every second monday doing a
live
q a which is wonderful many of the
people that i
are i have discussions with voices for
vicky come on there i believe
mary cohn is coming today i'm just
talking to her
i'm really glad to hear that most
importantly
for this the discord server is going to
be homing
creating a place in which we can do
the group practices that are often given
priority
within the wisdom of hypatia
reminded that we're doing this every
weekday morning at 9 30
eastern time reminder also
that continuity practice is more
important ensure quantity of practice
hold yourself to the standard of harsh
perfectionism
but a virtuous friendship because
there's no enemy worse than your own
mind and body there's no friend no ally
no true companion on the path
better than your own mind and body be
lamps unto yourselves
and to each other perhaps i'll see some
of you this afternoon
if not i hope to see you all on monday
it's a new dharma day we're going to
move forward again
with the epicureans within the wisdom of
hypatia take good care everyone